Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. London Office. Knowledge Centre subject files, 1941-2002 RL.11467
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Knowledge Centre Subject Files, 1941-2002; 1
  - 659.734 Pricing, 1973-1998; 3 folders (Box 24)
  - 659.734 Pricing, 1973-1998 (Box OV16)
  - 659.76 Point of Sale, 1974-2001 (Box 24)
  - 659.76 Point of Sale, 1974-2001 (Box OV16)
  - 659.78 Packaging, 1991-1999; 2 folders (Box 24)
  - 659.78 Packaging, 1991-1999; 2 folders (Box OV16)
  - 659.78 Packaging--Green/Eco-labeling, 1991-1992 (Box 24)
  - 659.780037 Packaging Regulations, 1977-1992 (Box 24)
  - 659.780037 Packaging Regulations, 1977-1992 (Box OV16)
  - 659.781 Packaging--Drinks, 1980-1998; 2 folders (Box 24)
  - 659.781 Packaging--Drinks, 1980-1998; 3 folders (Box 25)
  - 659.781 Packaging--Drinks, 1980-1998 (Box OV16)
  - 659.7815 Packaging--Aerosols, 1975-1997 (Box 25)
  - 659.7815 Packaging--Aerosols, 1975-1997 (Box OV16)
  - 663.1 Non-Alcoholic Drinks--General, 1989-1999; 5 folders (Box 25)
  - 663.1 Non-Alcoholic Drinks--General, 1989-1999; 2 folders (Box OV16)
  - 663.14 Tea, 1951-1993; 3 folders (Box 25)
  - 663.16 Fruit Juices, 1986-1999 (Box 25)
  - 663.16 Fruit Juices, 1986-1999 (Box OV16)
  - 663.17 Soft Drinks, 1986-2000; 6 folders (Box 25)
  - 663.17 Soft Drinks, 1986-2000; 2 folders (Box OV16)
  - 663.18 Carbonated Soft Drinks, 1986-1999; 4 folders (Box 26)
  - 663.18 Carbonated Soft Drinks, 1986-1999; 2 folders (Box OV16)
  - 663.22 Drinks--Low Alcohol, 1987-1996 (Box 26)
  - 663.22 Drinks--Low Alcohol, 1987-1996; 2 folders (Box OV17)
  - 663.3 Beer and Breweries, 1960-1998; 7 folders (Box 26)
  - 663.3 Beer and Breweries, 1960-1998; 3 folders (Box OV17)
  - 663.3 Beer and Breweries--Greene King's Bitters case study, 1988 (Box 26)
  - 663.31 Take-Home Beer (Cans, Bottles), 1987-1999; 2 folders (Box 26)
  - 663.31 Take-Home Beer (Cans, Bottles), 1987-1999 (Box OV17)
  - 663.32 Lager, 1989-2000; 3 folders (Box 26)
  - 663.32 Lager, 1989-2000; 2 folders (Box OV17)
  - 663.33 Real Ale (Cask Ale), 1975-1998; 2 folders (Box 26)
  - 663.33 Real Ale (Cask Ale), 1975-1998; 2 folders (Box OV17)
  - 663.35 Home Brewing, 1986-1991 (Box 26)
  - 663.35 Home Brewing, 1986-1991 (Box OV17)
  - 663.4 Cider, Perry, Alcopop, 1986-2000; 4 folders (Box 27)
  - 663.4 Cider, Perry, Alcopop, 1986-2000; 2 folders (Box OV17)
  - 663.5 Wine, 1993-2000; 4 folders (Box 27)
  - 663.5 Wine, 1993-2000; 2 folders (Box OV17)
  - 663.51 Cooler Drinks, 1986-1988 (Box 27)
  - 663.51 Cooler Drinks, 1986-1988 (Box OV18)
  - 663.6 Fortified Wines (Includes Port, Sherry), 1985-1998; 4 folders (Box 27)
  - 663.6 Fortified Wines (Includes Port, Sherry), 1985-1998; 2 folders (Box OV18)
  - 663.6 Fortified Wines (Includes Port, Sherry)--Coburn's Port Survey, 1989-1995 (Box 27)
  - 663.6 Fortified Wines (Includes Port, Sherry)--Harvey's Port and Sherry Surveys, 1992-1996 (Box 27)
  - 663.6 Fortified Wines (Includes Port, Sherry)--Sherry Institute of Spain, 1990-1995 (Box 27)
  - 663.7 Champagne, 1986-1998; 4 folders (Box 27)
  - 663.7 Champagne, 1986-1998 (Box OV18)
  - 663.8 Spirits, 1987-1999; 3 folders (Box 27)
  - 663.8 Spirits, 1987-1999; 2 folders (Box OV18)
  - 663.81 Whiskey, 1979-2000; 6 folders (Box 28)
  - 663.81 Whiskey, 1979-2000; 3 folders (Box OV18)
  - 663.82 Gin, 1978-2000; 3 folders (Box 28)
  - 663.82 Gin, 1978-2000 (Box OV18)
  - 663.83 Rum, 1970-1997; 3 folders (Box 28)
  - 663.83 Rum, 1970-1997; 2 folders (Box OV18)
  - 663.84 Brandy and Cognac, 1985-1998; 3 folders (Box 28)
  - 663.84 Brandy and Cognac, 1985-1998; 2 folders (Box OV18)
  - 663.84 Brandy and Cognac--Brandy de Jerez, 1993-1995 (Box 28)
  - 663.84 Brandy and Cognac--Le Cognac, 1985-1996 (Box 28)
  - 663.85 Vodka, 1984-1998 (Box 28)
  - 663.85 Vodka, 1984-1998 (Box OV18)
  - 663.86 Liqueurs, 1986-1998; 2 folders (Box 28)
  - 663.86 Liqueurs, 1986-1998 (Box OV19)
  - 663.9 Aperatifs and Vermouth, 1986-1997 (Box 28)
  - 663.9 Aperatifs and Vermouth, 1986-1997 (Box OV19)
  - 664 Delicatessen, 1983-1995 (Box 29)
  - 664 Delicatessen, 1983-1995 (Box OV19)
  - 664 Food and Food Industry, 1964-2001; 6 folders (Box 29)
  - 664 Food and Food Industry, 1964-2001; 2 folders (Box OV19)
  - 664.00037 Food Laws, 1981-1998; 10 folders (Box 29)
  - 664.00037 Food Laws, 1981-1998; 2 folders (Box OV19)
  - 664.00037 Food Laws--Booklets on food labeling, additives, misleading advertising claims, 1970-1992; 4 folders (Box 30)
  - 664.003 Food Prices, 1978-1996; 2 folders (Box 30)
  - 664.003 Food Prices, 1978-1996 (Box OV19)
  - 664.03 Organic Foods, 1990-2001 (Box 30)
  - 664.03 Organic Foods, 1990-2001 (Box OV19)
  - 664.0382 Food Production, 1968-2001; 2 folders (Box 30)
  - 664.0382 Food Production, 1968-2001; 2 folders (Box OV19)
  - 664.04 Synthetic Foods (Includes Genetically Modified Food, GMO, Quorn), 1980-1999; 3 folders (Box 30)
  - 664.04 Synthetic Foods (Includes Genetically Modified Food, GMO, Quorn), 1980-1999 (Box OV19)
  - 664.09 Food Franchising/Fast Food, 1985-2001; 4 folders (Box 30)
  - 664.09 Food Franchising/Fast Food, 1985-2001 (Box OV19)
  - 664.091 Ethnic Food, 1983-2001; 3 folders (Box 30)
  - 664.091 Ethnic Food, 1983-2001; 2 folders (Box OV19)
  - 664.095 Take-Away, 1977-1999; 2 folders (Box 30)
  - 664.095 Take-Away, 1977-1999; 2 folders (Box OV19)
  - 664.1 Confectionery, 1968-2000; 5 folders (Box 31)
  - 664.1 Confectionery, 1968-2000 (Box OV19)
  - 664.1 Confectionery--Booklets (Includes Cadbury; Cocoa, Chocolate and Confectionery Alliance; Nestle/Rowtree Mackintosh; Trebor Bassett), 1970-1998; 8 folders (Box 31)
  - 664.14 Chocolate Confectionery, 1984-1985; 2 folders (Box 31)
  - 664.14 Chocolate Confectionery, 1986-1997; 5 folders (Box 32)
  - 664.14 Chocolate Confectionery, 1986-1997; 2 folders (Box OV19)
  - 664.14 Chocolate Confectionery--Cadbury, 1991-1996; 2 folders (Box 32)
  - 664.15 Chewing Gum, 1980-2000 (Box 32)
  - 664.15 Chewing Gum, 1980-2000 (Box OV19)
  - 664.2 Flour and Flour Mills, 1960-1997; 3 folders (Box 32)
  - 664.2 Flour and Flour Mills, 1960-1997 (Box OV20)
  - 664.22 Baking Industry and Bakers, 1965-1996; 2 folders (Box 32)
  - 664.22 Baking Industry and Bakers, 1965-1996 (Box OV20)
  - 664.23 Bread, 1987-2000; 3 folders (Box 32)
  - 664.23 Bread, 1987-2000; 2 folders (Box OV20)
  - 664.24 Pasta and Rice, 1971-2000; 5 folders (Box 32)
  - 664.24 Pasta and Rice, 1971-2000; 2 folders (Box OV20)
  - 664.25 Food--Biscuits, 1975-1999; 5 folders (Box 32)
  - 664.25 Food--Biscuits, 1975-1999 (Box OV20)
  - 664.262 Food--Cakes, 1977-1999; 3 folders (Box 33)
  - 664.262 Food--Cakes, 1977-1999 (Box OV20)
  - 664.27 Food--Puddings and Desserts, 1976-1998; 2 folders (Box 33)
  - 664.27 Food--Puddings and Desserts, 1976-1998 (Box OV20)
  - 664.28 Food--Breakfast Cereals, 1970-1999; 4 folders (Box 33)
  - 664.28 Food--Breakfast Cereals, 1970-1999; 2 folders (Box OV20)
  - 664.29 Food--Ready Mixes, 1968-1997 (Box 33)
  - 664.29 Food--Ready Mixes, 1968-1997 (Box OV20)
  - 664.3 Food--Preservatives (Includes Irradiation), 1989-2001; 3 folders (Box 33)
  - 664.3 Food--Preservatives (Includes Irradiation), 1989-2001 (Box OV20)
  - 664.35 Food--Canned, 1987-1998 (Box 33)
  - 664.35 Food--Canned, 1987-1998 (Box OV20)
  - 664.35.634 Canned Fruit, 1967-1995; 2 folders (Box 33)
  - 664.35.641 Canned Meat, 1962-1994 (Box 33)
  - 664.35.641 Canned Meat, 1962-1994 (Box OV20)
  - 664.36 Pre-Packaged Foods, 1986-2001; 3 folders (Box 33)
  - 664.36 Pre-Packaged Foods, 1986-2001; 2 folders (Box OV20)
  - 664.5 Frozen Food, 1974-2001; 4 folders (Box 34)
  - 664.5 Frozen Food, 1974-2001 (Box OV20)
  - 664.5 Frozen Food--Birdseye Reports, 1964-1997; 5 folders (Box 34)
  - 664.55 Ice Cream, 1986-2000; 4 folders (Box 34)
  - 664.55 Ice Cream, 1986-2000; 2 folders (Box OV20)
  - 664.55 Ice Cream--Birdseye Wall's Reports, 1974-1992; 2 folders (Box 34)
  - 664.55 Ice Cream--Lyons Maid, 1980-1991; 2 folders (Box 34)
  - 664.6 Preserves, 1976-1999 (Box 34)
  - 664.6 Preserves, 1976-1999 (Box OV20)
  - 664.62 Jam, 1970-1998; 2 folders (Box 35)
  - 664.62 Jam, 1970-1998 (Box OV20)
  - 664.63 Marmelade, 1963-1997; 2 folders
  - 664.63 Marmelade, 1963-1997 (Box OV20)
  - 664.65 Table Jellies, 1962-1993; 2 folders
  - 664.658 Food Marketing/Packaging, 1962-1998; 4 folders
  - 664.658 Food Marketing/Packaging, 1962-1998 (Box OV20)
  - 664.7 Condiments, 1958-1997; 2 folders
  - 664.7 Condiments, 1958-1997 (Box OV20)
  - 664.71 Herbs, 1970-1998; 2 folders
  - 664.71 Herbs, 1970-1998 (Box OV20)
  - 664.72 Spices, 1970-1998; 2 folders
  - 664.72 Spices, 1970-1998 (Box OV20)
  - 664.74 Salt, 1974-1998; 3 folders
  - 664.74 Salt, 1974-1998 (Box OV20)
  - 664.76 Pickles and Sauces, 1984-1999; 2 folders
  - 664.76 Pickles and Sauces, 1984-1999; 2 folders (Box OV20)
  - 664.79 Salad Cream (Salad Dressing), 1964-1995; 2 folders
  - 664.79 Salad Cream (Salad Dressing), 1964-1995 (Box OV20)
  - 664.8 Soups, 1968-1998; 2 folders
  - 664.8 Soups, 1968-1998 (Box OV20)
  - 664.84 Meat and Fish Paste, 1980-1995
  - 664.87 Baby Goods (Including Food and Care), 1980-2000; 3 folders
  - 664.87 Baby Goods (Including Food and Care), 1980-2000 (Box OV20)
  - 664.87 Baby Goods (Including Food and Care)--Baby Care Booklets, 1988-1995; 2 folders (Box 36)
  - 664.87 Baby Goods (Including Food and Care)--Baby Food/Nutrition Booklets, 1981-1993; 2 folders (Box 36)
  - 664.87 Baby Goods (Including Food and Care)--Baby Products Market, 1990-1996 (Box 36)
  - 664.87 Baby Goods (Including Food and Care)--Baby Wipes and Nappies (Diapers), 1988-1993 (Box 36)
  - 664.8851 Cereal Bars, 1981-1992; 2 folders (Box 36)
  - 664.9 Crisps and Snacks, 1989-1999; 4 folders (Box 36)
  - 664.9 Crisps and Snacks, 1989-1999; 2 folders (Box OV20)
  - 664.9 Crisps and Snacks--KP Foods Publications, 1979-1993; 3 folders (Box 36)
  - 665.2 Animal Oils and Fats, 1969-1993 (Box 36)
  - 665.2 Animal Oils and Fats, 1969-1993 (Box OV21)
  - 665.3 Vegetable Oils and Fats, 1973-1997; 3 folders (Box 36)
  - 665.3 Vegetable Oils and Fats, 1973-1997 (Box OV21)
  - 665.5 Oil Industry, 1977-2001; 2 folders (Box 37)
  - 665.5 Oil Industry, 1977-2001 (Box OV21)
  - 665.51 Oil Industry Statistics, 1977-1996; 3 folders (Box 37)
  - 665.51 Oil Industry Statistics, 1977-1996 (Box OV21)
  - 665.561 Oil Industry--Motor Oil, 1974-1979 (Box 37)
  - 668.1 Detergents and Washing Powders, 1958-2000; 8 folders (Box 37)
  - 668.1 Detergents and Washing Powders, 1958-2000; 2 folders (Box OV21)
  - 668.2 Dishwashing Liquids, 1972-1995; 2 folders (Box 37)
  - 668.3 Toiletries and Cosmetics, 1980-2000; 6 folders (Box 37)
  - 668.3 Toiletries and Cosmetics, 1980-2000 (Box OV21)
  - 668.4 Soap, 1963-2000; 5 folders (Box 38)
  - 668.4 Soap, 1963-2000 (Box OV21)
  - 668.5 Facial Cosmetics, 1967-2000; 5 folders (Box 38)
  - 668.5 Facial Cosmetics, 1967-2000 (Box OV21)
  - 668.64 Oral Hygiene, 1985-2000; 3 folders (Box 38)
  - 668.64 Oral Hygiene, 1985-2000 (Box OV21)
  - 668.7 Hair Preparations, 1984-2000; 6 folders (Box 38)
  - 668.7 Hair Preparations, 1984-2000; 2 folders (Box OV21)
  - 668.71 Shampoos, 1984-1999; 3 folders (Box 38)
  - 668.71 Shampoos, 1984-1999 (Box OV21)
  - 668.8 Shaving Products, 1986-2000 (Box 38)
  - 668.8 Shaving Products, 1986-2000 (Box OV21)
  - 668.81 Men's Toiletries, 1986-2000; 2 folders (Box 39)
  - 668.81 Men's Toiletries, 1986-2000 (Box OV21)
  - 668.85 Depilatories, 1988-2000 (Box 39)
  - 668.9 Skin Care Products, 1984-2000; 4 folders (Box 39)
  - 668.9 Skin Care Products, 1984-2000; 2 folders (Box OV21)
  - 668.92 Suntan Lotions, 1984-2000; 3 folders (Box 39)
  - 668.92 Suntan Lotions, 1984-2000 (Box OV21)
  - 668.93 Deodorants, 1980-2000; 2 folders (Box 39)
  - 668.93 Deodorants, 1980-2000 (Box OV21)
  - 668.95 Perfumes, 1979-1998; 2 folders (Box 39)
  - 668.95 Perfumes, 1979-1998 (Box OV21)
  - 673.41 Diamonds, 1964-2000; 3 folders (Box 39)
  - 673.41 Diamonds, 1964-2000 (Box OV21)
  - 679.6 Tobacco, 1958-1999; 4 folders (Box 39)
  - 679.6 Tobacco, 1958-1999; 2 folders (Box OV22)
  - 679.62 Cigarettes, 1978-1998; 2 folders (Box 39)
  - 679.62 Cigarettes, 1978-1998 (Box OV22)
  - 679.63 Cigars, 1969-1992; 2 folders (Box 40)
  - 679.63 Cigars, 1969-1992 (Box OV22)
  - 679.64 Snuff/Smokeless Tobacco, 1964-1989 (Box 40)
  - 679.64 Snuff/Smokeless Tobacco, 1964-1989 (Box OV22)
  - 679.65 Smoker Requisites, 1971-1993 (Box 40)
  - 679.65 Smoker Requisites, 1971-1993 (Box OV22)
  - 679.651 Pipes, 1965-1990 (Box 40)
  - 679.651 Pipes, 1965-1990 (Box OV22)
  - 679.652 Matches, 1953-1994; 2 folders (Box 40)
  - 679.652 Matches, 1953-1994 (Box OV22)
  - 679.653 Lighters, 1962-1996; 2 folders (Box 40)
  - 679.653 Lighters, 1962-1996 (Box OV22)
  - 679.66 Smoking and Health, 1983-1999; 3 folders (Box 40)
  - 679.66 Smoking and Health, 1983-1999 (Box OV22)
  - 681.151 Electronics Industry, 1993-1998; 2 folders (Box 40)
  - 681.151 Electronics Industry, 1993-1998 (Box OV22)
  - 681.1512 Information Technology, 1984-1995 (Box 40)
  - 681.1512 Information Technology, 1984-1995 (Box OV22)
  - 681.1514 Semiconductors and Microchips, 1980-1996; 2 folders (Box 40)
  - 681.1514 Semiconductors and Microchips, 1980-1996 (Box OV22)
  - 681.1515 Computers, 1986-1999; 4 folders (Box 40)
  - 681.1515 Computers, 1986-1999; 3 folders (Box OV22)
  - 681.1515 Computers/Computer Industry, 1984-1999; 3 folders (Box OV23)
  - 681.1515A Computer Companies, 1984-1999; 3 folders (Box 40)
  - 681.1515A Computer Companies, 1984-1999 (Box OV23)
  - 681.1515B Computer Peripherals, 1985-1997 (Box 40)
  - 681.1515B Computer Peripherals, 1985-1997 (Box OV23)
  - 681.1516 Personal Computers, 1984-2000; 4 folders (Box 40)
  - 681.1516 Personal Computers, 1984-2000; 2 folders (Box OV23)
  - 681.1517 Computer Retailing, 1980-1996; 3 folders (Box 41)
  - 681.1518 Computer Software, 1985-1997; 2 folders (Box 41)
  - 681.1518 Computer Software, 1985-1997; 3 folders (Box OV23)
  - 681.1519 Computer Services, 1982-1997 (Box 41)
  - 681.1519 Computer Services, 1982-1997 (Box OV24)
  - 684.1141 Watches, 1979-2000 (Box 41)
  - 684.1141 Watches, 1979-2000; 2 folders (Box OV24)
  - 711 Town Planning, 1963-1997; 2 folders (Box 41)
  - 711 Town Planning, 1963-1997 (Box OV24)
  - 711 Town Planning--Milton Keynes, 1985-1988 (Box 41)
  - 711 Town Planning--Milton Keynes, 1985-1988 (Box OV24)
  - 721 Building Industry, 1986-1987 (Box OV24)
  - 741.68 Christmas and Greetings Cards, 1983-1997 (Box 41)
  - 741.68 Christmas and Greetings Cards, 1983-1997 (Box OV24)
  - 745 Industrial Design, 1988-1999; 2 folders (Box 41)
  - 745 Industrial Design, 1988-1999; 2 folders (Box OV24)
  - 778.5343 Industrial and Educational Films, 1970-1989; 3 folders (Box 41)
  - 778.5343 Industrial and Educational Films, 1970-1989 (Box OV24)
  - 796.063 Olympics, 1986-1998; 3 folders (Box 41)
  - 796.063 Olympics, 1986-1998; 2 folders (Box OV24)
  - 910 Travel and Tourism General, 1989-2000; 5 folders (Box 41)
  - 910 Travel and Tourism General, 1989-2000; 2 folders (Box OV25)
  - 910.1 Domestic Travel and Leisure, 1989-1999; 2 folders (Box 41)
  - 910.1 Domestic Travel and Leisure, 1989-1999 (Box OV25)
  - 910.2 Package Holidays and Tour Operators, 1986-1998; 2 folders (Box 42)
  - 910.2 Package Holidays and Tour Operators, 1986-1998 (Box OV25)
  - 910.3 Travel Agents, 1989-1995 (Box 42)
  - 910.3 Travel Agents, 1989-1995 (Box OV25)
  - 910.4 Tourism and Travel Advertising, 1970-1995; 2 folders (Box 42)
  - 910.4 Tourism and Travel Advertising, 1970-1995; 2 folders (Box OV25)
  - 910.5 Cruises, 1984-1999; 2 folders (Box 42)
  - 910.5 Cruises, 1984-1999; 2 folders (Box OV25)
  - 910.6 Business Travel, 1990-1999; 3 folders (Box 42)
  - 910.6 Business Travel, 1990-1999; 2 folders (Box OV25)
  - 929.74 Awards--General, 1986-1997; 2 folders (Box 42)
  - 929.74 Awards--General, 1986-1997; 2 folders (Box OV25)
  - 929.742 Supermarketing Awards, 1975-1995; 3 folders (Box 42)
  - 929.742 Supermarketing Awards, 1975-1995; 2 folders (Box OV25)
  - 940.06(E) Europe Advertising/Marketing/Media, 1994-2001 (Box 42)
  - 940.06(E) Europe Advertising/Marketing/Media, 1994-2001 (Box OV25)
  - 940.06(H) Europe/EEC Consumer Products, 1994-1999 (Box 42)
  - 940.06(H) Europe/EEC Consumer Products, 1994-1999 (Box OV25)
  - 973(E) U.S. Advertising/Marketing/Media, 1994-2000 (Box 42)
  - 973(E) U.S. Advertising/Marketing/Media, 1994-2000 (Box OV25)
  - 973(H) U.S. Consumer Products, 1993-1999 (Box 42)
  - 973(H) U.S. Consumer Products, 1993-1999 (Box OV25)
  - Subject Index, 1994 (Box 42)